<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Renzo's site</title><link>/education/</link><description>Recent content on Renzo's site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 01:14:35 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>QuickBooks_online_proadvisor</title><link>/education/quickbooks_online_proadvisor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 01:14:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/quickbooks_online_proadvisor/</guid><description>School/company: Intuit Title: QuickBooks Online Proadvisor Date range: 10/26/2023 - Present Overview: A certification to prove an individual&amp;rsquo;s ability to navigate and advice clients on the QuickBooks Online (QBO) platform.</description></item><item><title>Ocs</title><link>/education/ocs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 01:34:34 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/ocs/</guid><description>School/company: Alabama Military Academy Title: Officer Candidate Date range: 06/2023 - 08/2023 Overview: Officer Candidates are put into rigorous mental, educational, and physical training in order to produce high quality future leaders of the Army National Guard.</description></item><item><title>College</title><link>/education/college/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 20:39:58 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/college/</guid><description>School/company: The University of Southern Mississippi Major: Accounting, BS Date range: 2020 - 2024 Achievements: Accounting Scholars Leadership Workshop (AICPA ASLW 2022) President of Gulf Park Accounting Society (Fall 2022) Made my own website by learning HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and the Hugo</description></item><item><title>Intuit_bookkeeping_professional</title><link>/education/intuit_bookkeeping_professional/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 01:26:33 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/intuit_bookkeeping_professional/</guid><description>School/company: Intuit Title: Intuit Bookkeeping Professional Date: 02/07/2022 Overview: Have knowledge and understanding of accounting and bookkeeping principles (at least 150 hours of instruction) Endorsed by the American Council on Education for college credit (3 credits).</description></item><item><title>Powergenerator</title><link>/education/powergenerator/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 22:26:29 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/powergenerator/</guid><description>School/company: United States Army Title: Tactical Power Generation Date range: 2021 Overview: Basic electrical theory Basic understanding of a diesel engine How to read an electronic schematic Diagnose and repair parts of a tactical power generator utilized by the United States Army.</description></item><item><title>Smallarms</title><link>/education/smallarms/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2015 22:19:58 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/smallarms/</guid><description>School/company: United States Marine Corps Title: Small Arms Repairer/Technician Date range: 2015 Overview: General assembly and disassembly of the small arms weapons utilized by the United States Marine Corps (M9 Beretta, M16 Rifle and M4 Carbine, 50 Cal.</description></item><item><title>Highschool</title><link>/education/highschool/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 20:37:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/highschool/</guid><description>School/company: Eastern Technical Highschool Title: Student Date range: 2011 - 2015 Overview: Basic highschool education with some concentration in allied health.</description></item></channel></rss>