<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Renzo's site</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Renzo's site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 01:34:34 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ocs</title><link>/education/ocs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 01:34:34 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/ocs/</guid><description>School: Alabama Military Academy Title: Officer Candidate Date range: 06/2023 - 08/2023 Overview: Officer Candidates are put into rigorous mental, educational, and physical training in order to produce high quality future leaders of the Army National Guard.</description></item><item><title>Army_officer</title><link>/portfolio/army_officer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 01:26:37 -0500</pubDate><guid>/portfolio/army_officer/</guid><description>Branch: Mississippi Army National Guard Title: Platoon Leader / Army Officer Date range: 08/2023 Job Responsibilities: Platoon leader for a logistical unit.</description></item><item><title>College</title><link>/education/college/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 20:39:58 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/college/</guid><description>School: The University of Southern Mississippi Major: Accounting, BS Date range: 2020 - 2024 Achievements: Accounting Scholars Leadership Workshop (AICPA ASLW 2022) President of Gulf Park Accounting Society (Fall 2022) Made my own website by learning HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and the Hugo</description></item><item><title>Work Current</title><link>/portfolio/work-current/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 21:23:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>/portfolio/work-current/</guid><description>I currently work at a local accounting firm.</description></item><item><title>Schamber Jones CPA, PA</title><link>/portfolio/hattiesburg-firm/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 21:23:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>/portfolio/hattiesburg-firm/</guid><description>Company/Firm: Schamber Jones CPA, PA Title: Accounting Assistant Date range: May 2022 - December 2022 Job Responsibilities: Reconciled and categorized expenses and income of the firm and its clients.</description></item><item><title>The Grumpy Man LLC</title><link>/portfolio/the_grumpy_man/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 21:23:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>/portfolio/the_grumpy_man/</guid><description>Company/Firm: The Grumpy Man LLC Title: Bookkeeper Date range: Jan 2022 - May 2022 Job Responsibilities: Maintained and managed Accounts Receivable and Accounts Payable of two seperate entities (The Grumpy Man Foods and The Grumpy Man Distribution).</description></item><item><title>Powergenerator</title><link>/education/powergenerator/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 22:26:29 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/powergenerator/</guid><description>Branch: United States Army Title: Tactical Power Generation Date range: 2021 Brief Overview: Basic electrical theory Basic understanding of a diesel engine How to read an electronic schematic Diagnose and repair parts of a tactical power generator utilized by the United States Army.</description></item><item><title>The_home_depot</title><link>/portfolio/the_home_depot/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 21:23:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>/portfolio/the_home_depot/</guid><description>Company/Firm: The Home Depot Title: Seasonal Sales Associate Date range: May 2020 - October 2020 Job Responsibilities: Provided exceptional customer service to passing shoppers.</description></item><item><title>NCBC</title><link>/portfolio/ncbc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 21:23:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>/portfolio/ncbc/</guid><description>Company/Firm: The United States Marine Corps Title: Hazarous Material/Waste Coordinator and Deployment Insepector Rank: Cpl - Sgt Date range: 2018 - June 2020 Job Responsibilities: Ensured the armory compound&amp;rsquo;s compliance with the Resource Conservation and Recovery Act.</description></item><item><title>Smallarms</title><link>/education/smallarms/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2015 22:19:58 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/smallarms/</guid><description>Branch: United States Marine Corps Title: Small Arms Repairer/Technician Date range: 2015 Brief Overview: General assembly and disassembly of the small arms weapons utilized by the United States Marine Corps (M9 Beretta, M16 Rifle and M4 Carbine, 50 Cal.</description></item><item><title>Highschool</title><link>/education/highschool/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 20:37:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/highschool/</guid><description>School: Eastern Technical Highschool Title: Student Date range: 2011 - 2015 Brief Overview: Basic highschool education with some concentration in allied health.</description></item><item><title/><link>/refiles/karen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/refiles/karen/</guid><description>“A year from now you may wish you had started today.</description></item><item><title>About the Website</title><link>/about-website/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 0000 20:49:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>/about-website/</guid><description>I will list all the tools I used to create the website and how to install those tools for example I&amp;rsquo;m running linux-mint and windows 11 I also use the nix package manager and vs code sh &amp;lt;(curl -L https://nixos.</description></item></channel></rss>